[
    {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "SOECMUNITIONC",
        "Answer": "COMMUNICATION"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "NETIARWHG",
        "Answer": "NETWORKING"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "SFTOWRAE",
        "Answer": "SOFTWARE"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "FIREACENT",
        "Answer": "INTERFACE"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "TGDGEAS",
        "Answer": "GADGETS"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "DWNLOODA",
        "Answer": "DOWNLOAD"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "NNTNOVOAII",
        "Answer": "INNOVATION"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "ABTRYET",
        "Answer": "BATTERY"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "CTRUIIC",
        "Answer": "CIRCUIT"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "TOUPTU",
        "Answer": "OUTPUT"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "ICOAIPAPLTSN",
        "Answer": "APPLICATION"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "OPSOESRCR",
        "Answer": "PROCESSOR"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "IMFOCTORS",
        "Answer": "MICROSOFT"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "MRNPAGOGIMR",
        "Answer": "PROGRAMMING"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "NOHPTY",
        "Answer": "PYTHON"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "GARIMOLTH",
        "Answer": "ALGORITHM"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "ETANDITNINO",
        "Answer": "INDENTATION"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "ITNOPEARO",
        "Answer": "OPERATION"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "RAITUALFIC",
        "Answer": "ARTIFICIAL"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "MTANGRUE",
        "Answer": "ARGUMENT"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "ERISIFIDNET",
        "Answer": "IDENTIFIERS"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "ASILBREVI",
        "Answer": "VARIABLES"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "YRIBNA",
        "Answer": "BINARY"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "ITSWIBE",
        "Answer": "BITWISE"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "UBCKYICELPU",
        "Answer": "PUBLICKEY"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "ANEHRITNCEI",
        "Answer": "INHERITANCE"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "RANOSBATICT",
        "Answer": "ABSTRACTION"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "RUEFBF",
        "Answer": "BUFFER"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "OESCNOL",
        "Answer": "CONSOL"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "IRCAEYHCH",
        "Answer": "HIERARCHY"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "NOIEPTCEX",
        "Answer": "EXCEPTION"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "OLCIEPM",
        "Answer": "COMPILE"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "RSYIUCTE",
        "Answer": "SECURITY"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "CRTNTUIOSIN",
        "Answer": "INSTRUCTION"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "MAUTONTOAI",
        "Answer": "AUTOMATION"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "SWERILES",
        "Answer": "WIRELESS"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "ODYKEWR",
        "Answer": "KEYWORD"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "TGIRHEDN",
        "Answer": "THREADING"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "TEMMENILPI",
        "Answer": "IMPLEMENT"
     },
     {
        "quizTitle":"Tech Anagrams",
        "quizQuestion": "NOETMVELEPD",
        "Answer": "DEVELOPMENT"
     }
    ]